<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB &amp; REX Postprocess -- version V2.1.9 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
  <channel id="RedBull TV">
    <display-name lang="en">RedBull TV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://archive.org/download/RedBullTVLogo/Red-Bull-TV-Logo.png" />
    <url>http://www.redbull.tv</url>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20191019034300 +0000" stop="20191019040200 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Rob Meets Brook Macdonald</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Rob Meets</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Rob Warner travels all the way to New Zealand to meet with Brook Macdonald. Rob Warner travels all the way to New Zealand to meet with Brook Macdonald and the pair enjoy a boat ride. Get a look into Macdonald's home life and what he likes to do in his free time.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3 E5</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191019040200 +0000" stop="20191019042800 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Not Bad</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">30 days of mountain bike tomfoolery</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">An FMB dream team chronicles a 30-day saga of mountain bike shredding and tomfoolery in New Zealand. The best riders in the game travel to New Zealand for 30 days of epic mountain bike tomfoolery. The dream team going out to go big is Brett Rheeder, Brandon Semenuk, Brook Macdonald, Cam McCaul, Andrew Shandro, Ryan Howard and René Wildhaber.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191019042800 +0000" stop="20191019044000 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">TJ Rogers</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Ride to the Roots</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">From foster care to a first-class skateboarder, TJ Rogers heads home to retrace his turbulent formative years. Now a world-travelling skateboarder, TJ Rogers didn't always have it so easy. TJ returns to his hometown of Whitby, Canada, to visit the people and places that shaped his life during his troubled and turbulent formative years.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E6</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191019044000 +0000" stop="20191019044600 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Welcome aboard</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The Mediterranean Skateboard Cruise</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">The skateboarding crew check out the cruise ship and rip around some historic streets of Italy and Greece. The first leg of the Skate Cruise sets off from Rome and travels to Savona and Mykonos. With just hours to spend at each port, the sessions are fast paced and fully improvisational. There's no time to relax when you're a skateboarding tourist.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E1</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191019044600 +0000" stop="20191019045300 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Turkish delights</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The Mediterranean Skateboard Cruise</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">With more time to explore and great spots to skate, Turkey’s Izmir and Istanbul are the trip’s best stops yet. Turkey provides the trip’s best sessions so far, with more time to explore. Izmir offers some proper transition skating at the local park, and two days in Istanbul give the crew a chance to look for bigger street spots.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E2</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191019045300 +0000" stop="20191019045900 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">To infinity and beyond</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The Mediterranean Skateboard Cruise</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">The final leg sees the crew in Bulgaria and Greece. On the water, the ship’s deck is a skate spot with a view. On the last leg of the cruise, the skateboarding crew lands in Bulgaria to the warmest (albeit wettest) reception of the tour. Then it’s back to Greece, where the boys go to work on Athens’ marble with some eye-catching tricks.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E3</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191019045900 +0000" stop="20191019055300 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">VMax: No Straight Line</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Beating the mountain bike speed record, again</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Max Stöckl's quest to be the fastest man on a mountain bike takes him from Austria to the mountains of Chile. Markus 'Max' Stöckl has been setting speed downhill mountain bike records for over 20 years. Now, in his endless desire to go faster, he attempts to break his own World Record of 164.95kph on a desolate peak in Chile's Atacama Desert.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191019055300 +0000" stop="20191019060900 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Perfect Space</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">MacAskill's Imaginate</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Cyclist Danny MacAskill carries the Olympic Torch in Glasgow, Scotland, and searches for a film location. It's a once-in-a-lifetime honour for Danny MacAskill as he rides the Olympic Torch through the packed streets of Glasgow, Scotland. Work of his film project goes on with the search for a location yielding a surprisingly perfect space.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E3</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191019060900 +0000" stop="20191019061400 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Dropping in on Dubai</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Kriss Kyle rides his BMX off a helicopter</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Watch Kriss Kyle jump from a helicopter onto the roof of Burj Al Arab in Dubai – on his BMX bike. Despite a fear of heights Kriss Kyle jumps from a helicopter onto the roof of Burj Al Arab Jumeirah hotel in Dubai on his BMX bike. He then roams around as if it's a BMX playground made just for him.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191019062400 +0000" stop="20191019063100 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Madden Lake Mayhem</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Wakecation: Panama</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Parks Bonifay and crew head to Madden Lake for a glassy wake session in the middle of the Panamanian jungle. Parks Bonifay and crew head to Madden Lake for a glassy wake session in the middle of the Panamanian jungle. The remote sanctuary hosts some of the most pristine conditions of the trip, making way for an epic boat shredding session.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E4</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191019063100 +0000" stop="20191019064200 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Towing-In the Perfect Bay</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Wakecation: Panama</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">On the last day of the trip, the guys head to Portobelo and explore the historic ruins of the Caribbean coast. On the last leg of the trip, the guys head to Portobelo and explore the historic ruins of the Caribbean coast. After spending a day scouting some tow-in surfing locations, the crew finds the perfect bay to session out their vacation.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E5</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191019064200 +0000" stop="20191019074800 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Etnies: Album\t</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Touring five continents for skate spots</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">A passionate tribe of skateboarders search cities on five continents in a quest to find new skate spots. An eclectic tribe of skateboarders scour city streets across five continents in a quest to find new skate spots. This film by Etnies is an album of moments from the years that went into the project.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191019074800 +0000" stop="20191019075700 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Top action from Victoria</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Red Bull Skate of Origin 2019</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Watch the wild adventures going down in Victoria, Australia, for Red Bull Skate of Origin 2019. Watch the wild adventures going down in Victoria, Australia, featuring Jack Kirk, Callum Paul, Ricky Glaser and more for Red Bull Skate of Origin 2019.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191019075700 +0000" stop="20191019081200 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Cooking at the Catalan Grand Prix</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">MotoGP™: Inside Pass</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Host Vanessa Guerra is in Barcelona for Catalan GP, chatting with drivers on the track and in the kitchen. In Barcelona for the Catalan GP Vanessa Guerra challenges Pol Espargaró and Johann Zarco to a cooking challenge, then heads to the track to chat with drivers, and Marc Márquez show us his new livery.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E7</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191019081200 +0000" stop="20191019083700 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">B-Boys on the Road</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Break'n Reality</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Break'n Reality S1E2. Roxrite attends a BC One All-Stars workshop and makes a big decision about his immediate future. Lilou travels from France to visit his extended family in Algeria. Neguin heads home to Brazil but still struggles with his brother's death last year.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E2</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191019083700 +0000" stop="20191019090200 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Viking Velocity</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Ultimate Rush</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Downhill racer Erik Lundberg has a gravity-fuelled dream to break the world skateboard speed record. To break the current world speed record on a skateboard, downhill racer Erik Lundberg will have to go faster than 129.95kph (80.7mph). It's a feat that will make him rethink his motivations, his equipment and his commitment to his goal.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S5 E1</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191019090200 +0000" stop="20191019090600 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Freerunning in India</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Travel Story</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Ryan visits India for the first time and has some fun learning a new skill — Bollywood dancing. Ryan visits India for the first time and has some fun learning a new skill — Bollywood dancing. After mingling with the locals and jumping from city rooftops, Ryan does some parkour in front of the breathtaking Taj Mahal.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E4</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191019090600 +0000" stop="20191019090900 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">AWOLNATION – Kill Your Heroes</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Official music video from Red Bull Records</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">A group of kids are inspired to outrageous shenanigans by a group of bizarro-world Mister Rogers lookalikes. From their album Megalithic Symphony, AWOLNATION dresses up as a group of foul-mouthed, bizarro-world Mister Rogers lookalikes called The Milkmen and inspires a group of '60s children to rock-and-roll shenanigans.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191019090900 +0000" stop="20191019104800 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Roraima</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The climb of a lifetime</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">A trio of climbers launch an expedition to Mount Roraima, a South American peak shrouded in legend. Climbing partners Kurt Albert and Holger Heuber don't know what they're in for when they join competitive climbing superstar Stefan Glowacz for an expedition to Mount Roraima, a steep-walled South American peak shrouded in both rainforest and legend.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191019121500 +0000" stop="20191019124000 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Nino: the movie</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">A mountain biker’s quest for glory</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Follow Nino Schurter's story from his childhood in a remote Swiss mountain village to Olympic victory. Nino Schurter is one of the greatest mountain bikers in history. Follow him from his childhood in a remote Swiss mountain village to his greatest victory at the 2016 Summer Olympics in Rio de Janeiro.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
</tv>