<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB &amp; REX Postprocess -- version V2.1.9 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
  <channel id="RedBull TV">
    <display-name lang="en">RedBull TV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://archive.org/download/RedBullTVLogo/Red-Bull-TV-Logo.png" />
    <url>http://www.redbull.tv</url>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20191007023500 +0000" stop="20191007030100 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Pororoca</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Surfing the Amazon</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">A group of surfers travel to a remote part of the Amazon in an attempt to ride a destructive tidal wave. On every new and full moon, an enormous tidal wave occurs along the lower Amazon. It's a tempting target for surfers despite the many dangers involved, and it offers few who brave it the longest continuous rides of their lives.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191007030100 +0000" stop="20191007032900 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">ABC of... Surfing</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">ABC of..</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Discover some facts and figures of surfing, from its origins to the spectacular adrenaline-fuelled present. Learn some facts and figures of surfing, from its origins to the spectacular adrenaline-fuelled present that so many can’t live without. Surfing is a way of life for those who are hooked on it, and once you watch this you might be hooked too.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E11</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191007032900 +0000" stop="20191007035300 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">The Training Heats Up</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Break'n Reality</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">The b-boys train for the upoming BC One in Moscow. Lilou receives bad news and makes a strategic choice. When he discovers he can't compete in the BC One in Moscow, Lilou helps a fellow b-boy in order to beat his rival Neguin. In Sao Paulo, Neguin trains with his friend Andre. Roxrite gets an offer to compete in Moscow for the only title he's never won.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E4</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191007035300 +0000" stop="20191007044500 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Gotad Ad Kiangan</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Archaic Festivals</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">The ancestral heritage of the Ifugao of the Philippines is preserved in their Gotad Ad Kiangan festival. Being between the ancient and the modern, the Ifugao people of the Philippines continue their Gotad Ad Kiangan festival to preserve their fading heritage. It's a celebration of singing, dancing, and racing that culminates in a wrestling tournament.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E5</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191007044500 +0000" stop="20191007050000 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">The rise of VGM</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Diggin' in the Carts</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Explore the origins of Japanese video game music and its influence on modern-day musicians. From humble beginnings to worldwide recognition, Japanese video game music has inspired a generation. Meet Junko Ozawa, developer of the 'Namco sound', and iconic Nintendo composer Hirokazu Tanaka.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E1</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191007050000 +0000" stop="20191007052600 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Rob Meets Levi Sherwood</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Rob Meets</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Rob Warner travels to Palmerston North, New Zealand, to meet with freestyle motocross rider Levi Sherwood. Rob Warner travels to Palmerston North, New Zealand, to meet with freestyle motocross rider Levi Sherwood. The two talk about how Sherwood got to where he is at a young age and where he's headed.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3 E10</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191007052600 +0000" stop="20191007054100 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Close to home</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Red Bull Driftbrothers</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Elias and Johannes Hountondji feel the pressure as they race in their home country of Germany. It's time for Elias and Johannes Hountondji to race in their home country of Germany, where friends and family will be there to cheer them on. But having so many spectators raises the pressure.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E5</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191007054100 +0000" stop="20191007060900 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">ABC... of MotoGP™</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">ABC of..</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">From understanding the rules to learning the jargon, find out what makes this motorsport so thrilling. MotoGP™ is the premier class of motorbike racing. Get the lowdown on what makes this sport so thrilling. From understanding the rules to learning the jargon, here’s a crash course to get you up to speed on the basics of this elite motor sport.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E15</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191007060900 +0000" stop="20191007063100 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Choose Your Own Adventure</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Way Past Midnight</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Discover a party experience where every turn leads to a new and surreal part of an unforgettable night. More of an event than a party, Choose Your Own Adventure is all about letting go and living life as it unfolds. Go down the rabbit hole during a surreal night filled with food, music, and art, where the only certainty is an unforgettable experience.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E9</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191007063100 +0000" stop="20191007065400 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Global Warming</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Liquid Science</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">GZA, the show's host, travels the United States to explore how scientists are trying to solve global warming. Host GZA’s journey to discover how we might out-think global warming takes him from a Harvard RoboBee lab, to an underground park in New York, to the world’s largest hurricane simulator at the University of Miami.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E1</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191007065400 +0000" stop="20191007071400 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Transportation</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Liquid Science</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">GZA, founder of Wu-Tang Clan hip-hop band, investigates the future of transportation. To understand the future of transportation, host GZA looks at self-driving cars, pays a visit to the inventor of a personalised solar-powered rapid transit system, and rides a magnetic hover board.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E6</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191007071400 +0000" stop="20191007080200 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Aconcagua: A New Chance</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Dare to dream</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Runner Fernanda Maciel aims to be the first woman to climb up and down a 6,961m mountain in a day. Follow ultra-marathoner Fernanda Maciel as she travels to Argentina and attempts to become the first woman to climb up and down one of the highest mountains on the planet, the Aconcagua, in one day.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191007083000 +0000" stop="20191007083600 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Welcome aboard</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The Mediterranean Skateboard Cruise</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">The skateboarding crew check out the cruise ship and rip around some historic streets of Italy and Greece. The first leg of the Skate Cruise sets off from Rome and travels to Savona and Mykonos. With just hours to spend at each port, the sessions are fast paced and fully improvisational. There's no time to relax when you're a skateboarding tourist.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E1</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191007083600 +0000" stop="20191007084300 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Turkish delights</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The Mediterranean Skateboard Cruise</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">With more time to explore and great spots to skate, Turkey’s Izmir and Istanbul are the trip’s best stops yet. Turkey provides the trip’s best sessions so far, with more time to explore. Izmir offers some proper transition skating at the local park, and two days in Istanbul give the crew a chance to look for bigger street spots.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E2</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191007084300 +0000" stop="20191007084900 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">To infinity and beyond</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The Mediterranean Skateboard Cruise</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">The final leg sees the crew in Bulgaria and Greece. On the water, the ship’s deck is a skate spot with a view. On the last leg of the cruise, the skateboarding crew lands in Bulgaria to the warmest (albeit wettest) reception of the tour. Then it’s back to Greece, where the boys go to work on Athens’ marble with some eye-catching tricks.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E3</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191007084900 +0000" stop="20191007090300 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Red Bull Music Studio Sessions: Kelly Rowland</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Red Bull Music Studios Sessions</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Kelly Rowland and producers collaborate to share an artistic journey of music writing and recording. Go behind the scenes of a creative musical journey as a team of songwriters and producers write and record three tracks with superstar singer and artist Kelly Rowland at Red Bull Studios Los Angeles.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E1</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191007090300 +0000" stop="20191007093600 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Frozen Mind</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Riding Chamonix</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Pro snowboarder Victor De Le Rue has travelled the world, but his favourite place is Chamonix, France. Victor De Le Rue, a professional snowboarder from the Pyrenees, has ridden all over the world, but one particular place on Earth inspires him more than anywhere else: Chamonix, France.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191007093600 +0000" stop="20191007110100 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Against the Odds</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The gaming Cinderella story - EXCLUSIVE RELEASE ON AUGUST 7TH 3PM UTC</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">This is the journey of five Dota players and a coach, who, just two months before, had never played together. In 2018 Team OG were at rock-bottom, hit by painful departures and scrapping in qualifiers for Dota 2's T18. Against the Odds is the fairytale of this broken team's shot at Gaming’s biggest prize.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191007110100 +0000" stop="20191007111600 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Naming pasta and track turns in Italy</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">MotoGP™: Inside Pass</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Vanessa Guerra arrives in Italy's beautiful Tuscany and asks riders to describe the Mugello circuit. Vanessa Guerra arrives in Italy's beautiful Tuscany and asks riders to describe the Mugello circuit. Then it's time for pasta games, vlog takeovers and a ride around the track.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E6</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191007111600 +0000" stop="20191007120800 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">The Explorers</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Visions of Greatness</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Two determined innovators push their limits, risking all, in order to realise their dreams, are profiled. Pushing the limits of possibility challenges people who are willing to go beyond the visible horizon, no matter the risks. Documentary film-maker Jimmy Chin and XPRIZE creator Peter Diamandis are explorers who are always looking for a new frontier.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E4</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
</tv>