<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB &amp; REX Postprocess -- version V2.1.9 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
  <channel id="RedBull TV">
    <display-name lang="en">RedBull TV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://archive.org/download/RedBullTVLogo/Red-Bull-TV-Logo.png" />
    <url>http://www.redbull.tv</url>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20190927154200 +0000" stop="20190927155100 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Peter Conroy</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">This and Nothing Else</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Peter Conroy is a firefighter who runs into danger on a daily basis to feed his passion for chasing huge surf. Peter Conroy works in Dublin as a firefighter, and after bills are paid, he has about €50 for the month — which he puts towards surfing. Conroy's deep passion for chasing big waves at one of Ireland's scariest slabs is nothing short of inspiring.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E1</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>UR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190927155100 +0000" stop="20190927160300 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Barry Mottershead</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">This and Nothing Else</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">A self-employed South African relocates to Ireland to pursue his dream of surfing giant waves in the Atlantic. Barry Mottershead, a South African who now lives in Ireland, works as a kayak tour guide to make ends meet. But his passion lies in surfing the massive slabs at Mullaghmore. He is a man who charts his own course and does what it takes to surf.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E2</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>UR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190927160300 +0000" stop="20190927161400 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Andrew Cotton</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">This and Nothing Else</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">A family man works as a lifeguard full-time to be in the physical and financial shape to surf giant waves. Andrew Cotton is a lifeguard, a family man, and a Billabong XXL Award contender. He saves lives for a career as a lifeguard, builds homes with his bare hands as a necessity, and surfs the biggest waves he can find for fun.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E3</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190927161400 +0000" stop="20190927162800 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Hugo Vau</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">This and Nothing Else</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Being in the sea keeps this fisherman connected to his passion for surfing and lets him live the way he wants. Hugo Vau's life revolves around the ocean. He is a fisherman by trade, and for fun he surfs mountain-sized waves around the world. Being in the sea keeps him connected to his passion, makes him more confident, and lets him live the way he wants.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E4</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190927162800 +0000" stop="20190927163900 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">The kayak king</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Who is JOB</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">The crew finds an epic sand hill for Poopies to ride the kayak down in Maui. The crew is still on Maui hitting some killer waves on boards and kayaks then they find an epic sand hill for Poopies to ride the kayak down.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S7 E6</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>UR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190927163900 +0000" stop="20190927164200 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Last call for Mr Paul</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Jason Paul freeruns an airport</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">A lot of people run through an airport when they’re late for their flight. Pro freerunner Jason Paul just does it a little differently. A lot of people run through an airport when they’re late for their flight. Pro freerunner Jason Paul just does it a little differently, and along the way he sees parts of the airport most passengers never do.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190927164200 +0000" stop="20190927164500 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Jason Paul's arcade run</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Freerunning in 8-bit</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Freerunner Jason Paul takes his skills to the next level as he soars over pyramids and fights evil ninjas. Jason Paul and Team Farang come together to turn freerunning into an ‘80s arcade game. Soaring over pyramids, fighting ninjas, and thwarting the final boss, Jason takes his skills to the next level.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190927164500 +0000" stop="20190927184700 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Racing Together</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Motorcycle racing's journey</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">The history of motorcycle racing is charted through its best riders, from former legends to today’s stars. Discover the history of motorcycle racing through its key personalities, from former legends to today’s multi-title-winning, globetrotting riders, such as Mick Doohan, Valentino Rossi and Marc Márquez.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190927184700 +0000" stop="20190927191400 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Juxtapoz</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The Ripple Effect</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Robert Williams elevated Lowbrow to new heights by pioneering a magazine that championed the rebels of art. Blending the essences of punk rock, psychedelics, and pulp comics, Robert Williams invented the Lowbrow art movement. Shunned by traditional art media, he created a magazine to champion the misfits of the art world that led a creative revolution.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2 E4</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190927191400 +0000" stop="20190927194000 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">The Fedora</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Social Fabric</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Can the fedora be cool again? Kyle Ng meets up with the people at the heart of hat culture to find out. As popular as it is divisive, the fedora is a controversial accessory. Kyle Ng explores the Pachuco culture, meets a celebrity hatmaker, and travels to the United Kingdom to run with the Rude Boys, all to find out more about the infamous headwear.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E4</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190927194000 +0000" stop="20190927195200 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Ready, Aim, Skate</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Sheckler Sessions</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Ryan, David, and Kane head from Albuquerque to Denver, where they get to do some shooting before filming. Ryan, David, and Kane spend their final hours in Albuquerque filming party lines before hitting the road to David's hometown of Denver. The Mile High City gives them buttery ledges, smooth rails, and a shooting excursion with Dagger 8 Armory.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4 E9</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190927195200 +0000" stop="20190927201300 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Age of Ondra part 1</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Reel Rock</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Czech Republic's Adam Ondra has set out to be the best climber in every aspect, and he has achieved that. Czech Republic's Adam Ondra has set out to be the best climber in every aspect, and he has achieved that. Get inside Ondra's mind to find out what has fuelled him from such a young age.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S5 E2</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190927201300 +0000" stop="20190927203800 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Pressure Drop</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Ultimate Rush</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Brandon Semenuk goes for the ride of his life as he attempts to film his part for unReal in one shot. In an attempt to put his stamp on boundary-pushing videos, freeride mountain bike superstar Brandon Semenuk attempts to film his whole segment for unReal in a single take. Battling the clock and the odds, he has one shot to make history.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S5 E4</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190927203800 +0000" stop="20190927212900 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">The Flag Drops</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Driving Dirty</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">The preparation's done. All that now stands between the teams and their goal is 1,350km (840 miles) of desert. The months, even years, of preparation have led up to this moment. Now, all that stands between the five teams and their goal is 1,350km (840 miles) of punishing desert driving, where anything can happen.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E5</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190927212900 +0000" stop="20190927214500 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Naming pasta and track turns in Italy</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">MotoGP™: Inside Pass</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Vanessa Guerra arrives in Italy's beautiful Tuscany and asks riders to describe the Mugello circuit. Vanessa Guerra arrives in Italy's beautiful Tuscany and asks riders to describe the Mugello circuit. Then it's time for pasta games, vlog takeovers and a ride around the track.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E6</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190927214500 +0000" stop="20190927220000 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Cooking at the Catalan Grand Prix</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">MotoGP™: Inside Pass</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Host Vanessa Guerra is in Barcelona for Catalan GP, chatting with drivers on the track and in the kitchen. In Barcelona for the Catalan GP Vanessa Guerra challenges Pol Espargaró and Johann Zarco to a cooking challenge, then heads to the track to chat with drivers, and Marc Márquez show us his new livery.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E7</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190927220000 +0000" stop="20190927221300 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Testing communication skills</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">MotoGP™: Inside Pass</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Join Vanessa Guerra in the Netherlands for the TT Circuit Assen Grand Prix. Join Vanessa Guerra in the Netherlands for the TT Circuit Assen Grand Prix. Andrea Dovizioso takes over the vlog and shows us his paddock camp. Then it’s game, not race, time for the MotoGP™ riders.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E8</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190927221300 +0000" stop="20190927222800 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Getting close to fans in Germany</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">MotoGP™: Inside Pass</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Join host Vanessa Guerra as she takes us behind the scenes at MotoGP™ Germany in Sachsenring. Host Vanessa Guerra takes us to MotoGP™ Germany in Sachsenring, where she joins Honda's riders as they meet the fans, quizzes Suzuki's riders on super powers and gets the lowdown on MotoE™.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E9</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190927222800 +0000" stop="20190927232500 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Psychic Migrations</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Volcom's cerebral surf celebration</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Join a global wave-chasing odyssey that weaves together expressionistic surfing and a cerebral adventure. Shot in epic locations including the West Indies, Australia, Polynesia and the Americas, this celebration of surf stacks Volcom's surf team against the world's best waves in a cerebral adventure.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190927232500 +0000" stop="20190927235300 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">ABC of... Formula One</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">ABC of..</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Get a crash course in F1 racing, with lessons in the terminology, history, heroes and drama of the sport. Find out everything you need to know about the international motorsport of Formula One racing with facts and figures, as well as lessons in the terminology, disciplines, history, heroes, and drama of the sport.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E8</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
</tv>