<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB &amp; REX Postprocess -- version V2.1.9 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
  <channel id="RedBull TV">
    <display-name lang="en">RedBull TV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://archive.org/download/RedBullTVLogo/Red-Bull-TV-Logo.png" />
    <url>http://www.redbull.tv</url>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20190922122400 +0000" stop="20190922134900 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Against the Odds</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The gaming Cinderella story - EXCLUSIVE RELEASE ON AUGUST 7TH 3PM UTC</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">This is the journey of five Dota players and a coach, who, just two months before, had never played together. In 2018 Team OG were at rock-bottom, hit by painful departures and scrapping in qualifiers for Dota 2's T18. Against the Odds is the fairytale of this broken team's shot at Gaming’s biggest prize.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190922134900 +0000" stop="20190922144400 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Aragón – day 2</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Red Bull MotoGP™ Rookies Cup</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Follow day two of the final stop of the 2019 Red Bull MotoGP™ Rookies Cup in Aragón, Spain. Watch day two of the final stop of the 2019 Red Bull MotoGP™ Rookies Cup in Aragón, Spain. Motorland Aragón is a purpose-built, ultra-modern GP facility with dramatic earthworks providing racers with challenging changes in elevation.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190922144400 +0000" stop="20190922150400 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Music's Future</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Liquid Science</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">The legendary GZA, founder of Wu-Tang Clan, explores the future of music technology. Host GZA investigates the future of musical instrument technology at mi.mu and the Berklee College of Music, and freestyles with the future of music at Georgia Tech, United States.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E5</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190922150400 +0000" stop="20190922152600 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Escape. Create.</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Building the hardest downhill trail</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Dan Atherton designs intense BMX trails for himself and his sibling, brother Gee and sister Rachel. Something of a creative genius, mountain biker Dan Atherton designs intense, difficult trails for himself and his brother Gee, and sister Rachel. Watch as they perform amazing tricks on Dan's highly technical courses.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190922152600 +0000" stop="20190922153000 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Kriss Kyle's Kaleidoscope</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">See things differently</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Kriss Kyle performs a number of world-first tricks in an ever-changing environment designed to deceive. Kriss Kyle is widely regarded as one of the most creative BMX riders of his generation, and Kaleidoscope is his most ambitious project to date. See Kriss perform a number of world-first tricks in an ever-changing environment.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190922153000 +0000" stop="20190922155600 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Kriss Kyle's Kaleidoscope</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">See things differently</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Kriss Kyle performs a number of world-first tricks in an ever-changing environment designed to deceive. Kriss Kyle is widely regarded as one of the most creative BMX riders of his generation, and Kaleidoscope is his most ambitious project to date. See Kriss perform a number of world-first tricks in an ever-changing environment.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190922155600 +0000" stop="20190922160100 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Wee Day Out</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Danny MacAskill in Scotland</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Danny MacAskill tears around rural Scotland, setting out to capture the simple fun of a ride in the country. A relaxing day out in the Scottish countryside means something different for Danny MacAskill than it does for most people. With his signature trial riding style, Danny makes his way over hay bales, through forests and all along the rolling hills.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190922160100 +0000" stop="20190922160500 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">AWOLNATION – Kill Your Heroes</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Official music video from Red Bull Records</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">A group of kids are inspired to outrageous shenanigans by a group of bizarro-world Mister Rogers lookalikes. From their album Megalithic Symphony, AWOLNATION dresses up as a group of foul-mouthed, bizarro-world Mister Rogers lookalikes called The Milkmen and inspires a group of '60s children to rock-and-roll shenanigans.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190922160500 +0000" stop="20190922162900 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">B-Boys on the Road</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Break'n Reality</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Break'n Reality S1E2. Roxrite attends a BC One All-Stars workshop and makes a big decision about his immediate future. Lilou travels from France to visit his extended family in Algeria. Neguin heads home to Brazil but still struggles with his brother's death last year.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E2</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190922162900 +0000" stop="20190922165500 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Viking Velocity</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Ultimate Rush</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Downhill racer Erik Lundberg has a gravity-fuelled dream to break the world skateboard speed record. To break the current world speed record on a skateboard, downhill racer Erik Lundberg will have to go faster than 129.95kph (80.7mph). It's a feat that will make him rethink his motivations, his equipment and his commitment to his goal.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S5 E1</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190922165500 +0000" stop="20190922165800 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Freerunning in India</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Travel Story</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Ryan visits India for the first time and has some fun learning a new skill — Bollywood dancing. Ryan visits India for the first time and has some fun learning a new skill — Bollywood dancing. After mingling with the locals and jumping from city rooftops, Ryan does some parkour in front of the breathtaking Taj Mahal.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E4</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190922165800 +0000" stop="20190922171900 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Surfing at J-Bay 2019</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">No Contest</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">At J-Bay, South Africa, a selection of visiting and local pros feast on several days' worth of flawless walls. As winter set in at J-Bay, in South Africa, a selection of visiting and local pros feasted on several days' worth of flawless walls at the world's best right-hander.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2 E6</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190922171900 +0000" stop="20190922172800 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Heading Down Under</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Who is JOB</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Jamie O'Brien and the surf crew kick off the show's final season with the madness that only they can deliver. Jamie O'Brien and the whole crew kick off the show's final season with the madness that only they can deliver. Heading from Hawaii to Australia, the guys take a motorhome all over the coast.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S8 E1</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190922172800 +0000" stop="20190922173700 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Kayaks, barrels and powder mountain</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Who is JOB</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Jamie O’Brien and Poopies get up bright and early to go river surfing. Jamie O’Brien and Poopies get up bright and early to start river surfing. Then Poopies gets a serious dose of powder mountain before he and the crew go chasing barrels on kayaks.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S7 E1</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>UR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190922173700 +0000" stop="20190922180700 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Beneath the Surface</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Chasing a secret slab</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Big wave surfer Andrew Cotton rolls the dice on his season by choosing to explore a wave with huge potential. Big wave surfer Andrew Cotton risks his whole season on an unexplored piece of the Atlantic that could hold the biggest wave to ever be ridden. He travels to the middle of the ocean looking for the next big swell, but the ocean offers no guarantees.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190922200200 +0000" stop="20190922210200 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Moto 9</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The world's best places for riding</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Journey to the world's most incredible riding locations with riders who are worthy of such venues. Journey to the world's most incredible riding locations with riders who are worthy of such venues in Moto 9, the latest of the world's most progressive moto video franchise.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190922210200 +0000" stop="20190922220500 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Standing on Water</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Passion Overcomes Fear</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Casper Steinfath is a man with a goal to be the best stand up paddle surfer, despite being terrified of water. Casper Steinfath comes from a small, isolated fishing village in Denmark, and he is deathly afraid of water. He also wants to become one of the best stand up paddle surfers in the world. This is the story of what happens when passion overcomes fear.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190922220500 +0000" stop="20190922222100 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Hanging Spear</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Headwaters of the Hudson</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">World class whitewater kayakers Steve Fisher and Pat Keller explore the Hanging Spear Gorge. Join world class whitewater kayakers Steve Fisher and Pat Keller as they explore the Hanging Spear Gorge of the Opalescent River, the highest source of the Hudson and the deepest part of New York State’s High Peaks wilderness.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190922222100 +0000" stop="20190922224800 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Pororoca</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Surfing the Amazon</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">A group of surfers travel to a remote part of the Amazon in an attempt to ride a destructive tidal wave. On every new and full moon, an enormous tidal wave occurs along the lower Amazon. It's a tempting target for surfers despite the many dangers involved, and it offers few who brave it the longest continuous rides of their lives.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190922224800 +0000" stop="20190922225400 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Top action from New South Wales</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Red Bull Skate of Origin 2019</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Watch the wild adventures going down in New South Wales, for Red Bull Skate of Origin 2019. Watch the wild adventures going down in New South Wales, Australia, featuring Jake Hayes, Dane Burman, Rob Pace and more for Red Bull Skate of Origin 2019.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
</tv>