<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB &amp; REX Postprocess -- version V2.1.9 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
  <channel id="RedBull TV">
    <display-name lang="en">RedBull TV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://archive.org/download/RedBullTVLogo/Red-Bull-TV-Logo.png" />
    <url>http://www.redbull.tv</url>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20191001150400 +0000" stop="20191001155500 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">The Unifiers</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Visions of Greatness</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Artists like Wyclef Jean and Paul van Dyk may have grown up isolated, but now seek to bring people together. Despite growing up on different sides of the globe, Paul van Dyk and Wyclef Jean shared the experience of an early life filled with strife and isolation. But these great artists channelled that into an unquenchable desire to bring people together.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E7</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191001155500 +0000" stop="20191001162200 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">ABC of... Cliff diving</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">ABC of..</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Get to know the art of falling as the top divers give an inside look at cliff diving. Get to know the art of falling as the top divers give an inside look at cliff diving. Jumping from almost three times the olympic height these divers find a way to look past fear and take a leap.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E18</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191001162200 +0000" stop="20191001165000 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Rainbow Dive</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Rhiannan Iffland's journey of discovery</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Rhiannan Iffland journeys to the Australian Outback and uncovers more than she expected. World champion cliff diver Rhiannan Iffland  journeys to the Australian Outback to rediscover her sense of self and love for diving and in the process uncovers a whole lot more than she bargained for.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191001165000 +0000" stop="20191001170400 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Jeffreys Bay</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Beyond the Lines</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Kanoa Igarashi goes behind the scenes at the WSL Men's Championship Tour at Jeffreys Bay, South Africa. Join Kanoa Igarashi as the Japanese surfer goes behind the scenes at the sixth stop of the WSL Men's Championship Tour at Jeffreys Bay, South Africa.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E2</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191001170400 +0000" stop="20191001175700 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Sébastien Loeb: Off Roads</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The WRC's best take on the Dakar</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Sébastien Loeb and co-driver Daniel Elena made WRC history. In 2016 they took on a new challenge: Dakar. Sébastien Loeb and his co-driver, Daniel Elena, made history racing in the WRC, winning a record nine world titles together. In 2016 they raced together once again and took on a new challenge: the famous Dakar off-road race.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191001175700 +0000" stop="20191001180600 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">The Hansen Brothers goes Höljes</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The Hansen Brothers</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Ever wondered what made Kevin and Timmy Hansen into who they are today? Find out what drives these brothers. Ever wondered what made Kevin and Timmy Hansen into who they are today, and what spurs them on to excel within their sport? Find out what drives these driftbrothers to thrive.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2 E1</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191001180600 +0000" stop="20191001183600 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Road to 55</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The Drive to Become a Formula One Racer</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Experience the 2014 Formula One racing season with Carlos Sainz as he strives to become a top driver. Experience the 2014 Formula One racing season with Carlos Sainz as he strives to become a top driver. Meet the team behind his success and feel his highs and lows.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191001183600 +0000" stop="20191001184400 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">A Door in the Sky</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The Soul Flyers</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Get to know the Soul Flyers and see what went into making a ground-breaking BASE jump happen. Get to know the Soul Flyers, Fred Fugen and Vince Reffet, who make history by BASE jumping from a mountain then flying right through an aircraft's door. See what went into making this ground-breaking jump happen.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191001184400 +0000" stop="20191001184600 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">The Soul Flyers</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">A Door in the Sky: Extra</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">In a world first, the Soul Flyers wingsuit pilots BASE jump off a mountain and land in a mid-air aeroplane. Above the Alps, the Soul Flyers, Fred Fugen and Vince Reffet, make history by BASE jumping from a mountain, catching a Pilatus plane in their wingsuits, then flying right through the aircraft's door – a world first!</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191001184600 +0000" stop="20191001191100 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">The Leather Jacket</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Social Fabric</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">A bit of cowhide that never fails to stand out, the leather jacket is a style icon the world over. Made for bomber pilots, adopted the world over, the leather jacket is a true style icon. Kyle Ng gets punk in Tokyo, Japan, races around Brooklyn, New York, United States, and meets the father of the over-the-top 'championship jacket'.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E7</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191001191100 +0000" stop="20191001194100 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Budapest</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The Road Trick</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Magician Adam Trent discovers that Budapest, Hungary, has a light and dark side. Can his tricks work in both? The first stop of magician Adam Trent's European journey is the party city of Budapest, Hungary. Adam wants to see the things that the tourists don't, but walking on the dark side has its risks. Can Adam's magic get him out of a dangerous situation?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E1</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191001194100 +0000" stop="20191001195300 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Rising swell and womp life</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Who is JOB</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">It's a new season for Wompers and as the guys find a way to modify their Wompers, will it mean fewer wipeouts? Jamie O'Brien and the crew play a game of risk surfing, kayaking and tubing off rocks on Hawaii's North Shore. It's a new season for Wompers and as the guys find a way to modify their own Wompers, will it mean fewer wipeouts?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S7 E2</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>UR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191001195300 +0000" stop="20191001200200 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">A Day at the Office</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Sheckler Sessions</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">The skate sculpture at the Red Bull office is being retired, so Ryan and the gang give it a proper send-off. Red Bull naturally has an office that could double as a skate park, so when they are retiring their giant in-office ramp, Ryan and friends come by to skate it one last time. The guys also spend time reliving their favorite moments from the year.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4 E10</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191001200200 +0000" stop="20191001201400 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Lincoln Skatepark</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Official Skatepark Review</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Joey Brezinski reviews Lincoln Skatepark in Los Angeles to see what it has to offer. Joey Brezinski reviews Lincoln Skatepark in Los Angeles to see what it has to offer. Although it's not his favourite park, Brezinski and 'Rip' still manage to do some shredding.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E4</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191001201400 +0000" stop="20191001201900 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Chengdu, China</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The Way to Everest</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">The crew assembles in Chengdu, China, and starts the trip off right with some killer sessions and good times. Despite crazy traffic and enthusiastic security guards, the first stop of the journey in Chengdu, China, has good times and good skating aplenty. After exploring the city, shredding everything they can, it's off to Lhasa, the capital of Tibet.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E1</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191001201900 +0000" stop="20191001202500 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Lhasa, Tibet</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The Way to Everest</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Lhasa, Tibet, provides some killer spots for the skateboarders to skate while they acclimate to the altitude. At 3,600 metres above sea level, Lhasa, Tibet, is the first experience with high-altitudes for the team of skateboarders. Between the city's welcoming locals and marble architecture, there's no shortage of killer sessions, just shortness of breath.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E2</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191001202500 +0000" stop="20191001203500 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">The Road to Base Camp</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The Way to Everest</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">On the road to Mount Everest Base Camp, the crew stops to skate in some spots with breathtaking backdrops. The road to Mount Everest is lined with monasteries, villages, towns, with loads of breathtaking backdrops. Everyone has a blast skating their way to Everest Base Camp, except Madars Apse, who was grounded in Lhasa, Tibet, after a heavy slam.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E3</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191001203500 +0000" stop="20191001204000 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">Top action from Queensland</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Red Bull Skate of Origin 2019</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Watch the wild adventures going down in Queensland, Australia, for Red Bull Skate of Origin 2019. Watch the wild adventures going down in Queensland, Australia, featuring Jackson Pilz, Jake Duncombe, Jesse Noonan and more for Red Bull Skate of Origin 2019.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191001204000 +0000" stop="20191001210800 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">ABC of... Hard Enduro</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">ABC of..</sub-title>
    <desc lang="en">Take a down-and-dirty crash course in all things Hard Enduro, motocross's toughest discipline. Hard Enduro is motocross's toughest discipline and demands a special type of madness to compete in it. From learning the lingo to discovering more about the pro riders, take a crash course in an event where just finishing is victory in itself.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1 E1</episode-num>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20191001210800 +0000" stop="20191001223900 +0000" channel="RedBull TV">
    <title lang="en">On Any Sunday: The Next Chapter</title>
    <desc lang="en">Motorcycles and Those Who Ride. The Brown family continue their tradition of documentary filmmaking. On Any Sunday: The Next Chapter captures the passion for motorcycle riding first portrayed in the original film in 1971 and continues today.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Sports</category>
    <rating system="US">
      <value>NR</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
</tv>