<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB &amp; REX Postprocess -- version V2.1.9 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
  <channel id="Channel 5">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel 5</display-name>
    <url>http://www.toggle.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Channel 8">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel 8</display-name>
    <url>http://www.toggle.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Channel U">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel U</display-name>
    <url>http://www.toggle.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Suria">
    <display-name lang="en">Suria</display-name>
    <url>http://www.toggle.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Channel NewsAsia">
    <display-name lang="en">Channel NewsAsia</display-name>
    <url>http://www.toggle.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Vasantham">
    <display-name lang="en">Vasantham</display-name>
    <url>http://www.toggle.sg</url>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20190823003000 +0800" stop="20190823013000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">黄金光辉的人生 My Golden Life  - EP 9</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Daojing sees Zhi-an at home and assumes that she has gone to his house to threaten and blackmail him. He gives her a scolding and is extremely embarrassed when he hears later that Zhi-an is Enshi. (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)道京在家里看到知安，以为知安故意找上门威胁及敲诈他，于是不分青红皂白地把她大骂一顿。道京知道知安就是恩石后觉得尴尬不已。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190823013000 +0800" stop="20190823023000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">黄金光辉的人生 My Golden Life  - EP 10</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Mingxi wants Zhi-an to spend a big sum of money in one day. Zhi-an buys gifts for the Xu family happily. However, Zhi-xiu is unappreciative and wants Zhi-an not to treat them like beggars.  (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)明熙要知安在一天内花完三千万韩元。知安开心地买礼物给徐家的家人们，知秀却不领情，不但不接受，还要知安别把他们当成乞丐。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190823023000 +0800" stop="20190823110000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190823110000 +0800" stop="20190823150000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">JML Home Shopping - Infomercial</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190823150000 +0800" stop="20190823163000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">金装律师 Suits  - EP 9</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) A deliberate act to cover up criminal evidence by Bingxu 12 years ago caused Kangshuo to send Zhang Xixian to jail wrongfully. Kangshuo hopes to apply for a re-trial, but he encounters rejections by Xixian and his colleagues at the law firm. (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)由于炳旭当年湮灭证据导致康硕在12年前误将张锡贤定为杀人犯。康硕希望申请再审，但锡贤对他很抗拒，律师楼的同事也不同意康硕的想法。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190823163000 +0800" stop="20190823170000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">我也可以是韩星 Miss Korea - EP 9</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) In the new season of Miss Korea, 2 young ladies from totally different cultures and background (one Chinese who lives in Australia &amp; the other Singaporean) will leave the comfort of their homes and embark on a 3 months journey to fulfil a K-Pop dream in Korea...  (重)两个来自完全不同文化和生活背景的女生Julia和Jojo为了完成她们的韩星梦,远赴韩国进行3个月的造星训练。在人生地不熟的环境下,两个女生可否能和睦共处? 他们会实现梦想吗? 敬请期待!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190823170000 +0800" stop="20190823180000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">我女婿的女人 Marrying My Daughter Twice  - EP 27</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Xiantai decides not to agree to Zaiyong's condition as Yingcai cannot return to life even if the hit-and-run driver is found. (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)贤泰觉得就算找到目击者，也可能捉不到肇事逃逸者，即使捉到，英彩也不可能起死回生，于是在经过深思熟虑后决定不跟载永做交易。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190823180000 +0800" stop="20190823190000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">医疗船 Hospital Ship  - EP 11</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Zaijie's mother comes on board to persuade Zaijie to quit his job, but Enzai discovers that she has heart blockage. Zaijie cannot do anything so Enzai helped to operate on her. Zaijie developed a liking to her.  (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)载杰的妈妈来到医疗船，打算劝儿子回去。交谈其间，恩在发现她患有心肌梗塞。载杰无能为力，最终恩在成功为载杰的妈妈动手术，此时，载杰对恩在起了好感。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190823190000 +0800" stop="20190823200000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">黄金光辉的人生 My Golden Life  - EP 11</title>
    <desc lang="en">Xianyu He assumes that Zhi-an has betrayed her conscience and taken up immoral jobs when Zhi-an appears before him, decked out in branded clothing. Zhi-an does not want to tell Xianyu He that she has acknowledged the Cuis for money's sake and hence keeps the truth from him.  (PG)(双声道-中/韩)鲜于赫看到知安光鲜亮丽地出现在他面前，怀疑她为了钱出卖色相。知安不想让鲜于赫知道她为了钱跟崔氏夫妻相认，于是没有把真相告诉他。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190823200000 +0800" stop="20190823210000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">黄金光辉的人生 My Golden Life  - EP 12</title>
    <desc lang="en">Zhitai questions Xiuya angrily when he bumps into her on a date with another man. Xiuya defends herself by saying that she is looking for other alternatives as Zhitai does not want to marry her. Taixiu is sad to hear Zhitai say that he cannot marry Xiuya because his family is poor.  (PG)(双声道-中/韩)知泰撞见秀雅跟他人相亲，于是怒气冲冲地质问秀雅。秀雅理直气壮，说她想结婚了，但知泰不肯，所以只好另寻伴侣。两人在街上大吵，被太修看到。太修听到知泰说他不结婚的理由是因为家里没钱，于是难过不已。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190823210000 +0800" stop="20190823220000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">进击的台湾 2 Hello Taiwan S2 - EP 7</title>
    <desc lang="en">This programme takes a look at some of Taiwan's famous eateries and dishes. Most importantly, the programme also reveals the moving story behind its success. 介绍台湾当地的美食与它们成功背后的故事.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190823220000 +0800" stop="20190823230000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">同盟 The Unholy Alliance  - EP 28</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this concluding episode, "Rainman returns to seek revenge. Ling Xi and Anthony turn against each other as they make their last attempt to take control of their company. To save their mother who has been kidnapped, Zijie and Kent accept a challenge for a final showdown with "Rainman".   (PG13-暴力镜头)(大结局)在这大结局里，失踪已久的"Rainman"，终于再度现身，为复仇而来。令熹与令家和趁令熊不在，争坐主席的位子而互相残杀。 子杰和千佑两兄弟，为了救出遭绑架的母亲，被逼接受挑战，与"Rainman"一决高下。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190823230000 +0800" stop="20190823233000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻 News Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">A comprehensive half-hour news programme, NEWS TONIGHT provides viewers with important local, international and financial developments for the day. U频道《晚间新闻》，在半小时里除深入报道本地与国际要闻，还有详尽的财经新闻和体坛动态。世界局势与经济动脉，让大家轻松掌握。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190823233000 +0800" stop="20190824000000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">进击的台湾 2 Hello Taiwan S2 - EP 7</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) This programme takes a look at some of Taiwan's famous eateries and dishes. Most importantly, the programme also reveals the moving story behind its success. (重)介绍台湾当地的美食与它们成功背后的故事.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190824000000 +0800" stop="20190824003000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">进击的台湾 2 Hello Taiwan S2 - EP 7</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) This programme takes a look at some of Taiwan's famous eateries and dishes. Most importantly, the programme also reveals the moving story behind its success. (重)介绍台湾当地的美食与它们成功背后的故事.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190824003000 +0800" stop="20190824013000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">黄金光辉的人生 My Golden Life  - EP 11</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Xianyu He assumes that Zhi-an has betrayed her conscience and taken up immoral jobs when Zhi-an appears before him, decked out in branded clothing. Zhi-an does not want to tell Xianyu He that she has acknowledged the Cuis for money's sake and hence keeps the truth from him.  (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)鲜于赫看到知安光鲜亮丽地出现在他面前，怀疑她为了钱出卖色相。知安不想让鲜于赫知道她为了钱跟崔氏夫妻相认，于是没有把真相告诉他。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190824013000 +0800" stop="20190824023000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">黄金光辉的人生 My Golden Life  - EP 12</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Zhitai questions Xiuya angrily when he bumps into her on a date with another man. Xiuya defends herself by saying that she is looking for other alternatives as Zhitai does not want to marry her. Taixiu is sad to hear Zhitai say that he cannot marry Xiuya because his family is poor.  (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)知泰撞见秀雅跟他人相亲，于是怒气冲冲地质问秀雅。秀雅理直气壮，说她想结婚了，但知泰不肯，所以只好另寻伴侣。两人在街上大吵，被太修看到。太修听到知泰说他不结婚的理由是因为家里没钱，于是难过不已。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190824023000 +0800" stop="20190824080000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190824080000 +0800" stop="20190824100000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">JML Home Shopping - Infomercial</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190824100000 +0800" stop="20190824120000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">最强大脑 第四季 The Brain China S4 - EP 7</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) The Brain is a talent show that celebrates gifted minds and incredible skills of extraordinary men, women, and children. In Season 4, the programme aims to disseminate scientific knowledge to more viewers, especially the youths. Tune in as popular artistes take up different challenges in each episode. (重)《最强大脑》是一个大型科学类脑力真人秀节目。第四季主打“让科学在年轻人中流行起来”，以青春为科学站台，向年轻人传播科学的重要性，并请来年轻人喜欢的青春偶像参加挑战。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190824120000 +0800" stop="20190824123000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">大飨宴 The Banquet - EP 7</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) An info series featuring cultural celebrations in various parts of the world. The programme will feature the highlight of the celebrations; "The Banquet". (重)《大飨宴》在每一集里呈现不一样的节庆或食会 - 全部8个海外地点的8大飨宴。节目将从整个设宴地点和宴会背景说起，进而聚焦各个人物以及宴会上的特别菜肴。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190824123000 +0800" stop="20190824131000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">北京到莫斯科 Beijing To Moscow  - EP 9</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Upon arriving in Moscow, the trio hit the ground running, asking locals about the name of the lullaby. At last, a busker triggers some of Kai Xiang's memories. The lullaby was something Kloudiia sang to her son, An Ran. They turn to Kloudiia's alma mater where they manage to get an address off an old friend. The landlord reveals that Kloudiia once tried to commit suicide here. As Kai Xiang's frustration escalates, Kenneth suggests asking the police for help and a name comes up, Li Mei Ling. (PG-部分画面令人不安)(重)在莫斯科。三人刚下火车，就急忙询问当地人该歌曲的名字，最后是一个街头艺人唤醒了凯翔的一些记忆。那是一首Kloudiia对孩子经常唱起的儿歌。孩子的名字叫安然。三人来到Kloudiia曾经在这里留学的莫斯科艺术学校。通过Kloudia的同学，找到了Kloudiia曾经居住的公寓。当房东得知三人是来寻找Kloudiia的，就马上显露出极不友善的表情，原来Kloudiia曾在这里自杀。Kloudiia还活着吗？在凯翔几近崩溃的状态下，Kenneth 提议请警察帮忙找Kloudiia，警察随后提供了一个关键人物——李美玲。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190824131000 +0800" stop="20190824133000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">混口饭吃而已 Hear My Thoughts - EP 9</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Familiar real-life scenarios with hilarious caricature, Hear My Thoughts brings to attention the bottled-up sentiments of people at their workplace. (重)幽默短片《混口饭吃而已》，以逗趣的方式叙述各行各业的酸甜苦辣！打工仔的内心喊话及苦衷——只有自己最清楚，真相也绝非你所能想象！演员阵容包括：田铭耀、鐘琴、王智荟、胡佳嬑、坤华、罗翊绮及林茜茜，还有客串嘉宾周崇庆、权怡凤、朱厚任等。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190824133000 +0800" stop="20190824143000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">线人 3 Fixer 3 - EP 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Fixer is a group of righteous people who helps to uphold social justice, exposing the truth of reality and create social awareness. Through their reporting power and intervention, the people and issues involved can get the right attention and assistance. Thus, revealing the truth and hidden stories. (重)线人，一群维护社会公平正义，揭露事实真相的义士，借助他们采访社会议题的力量，透过他们的介入，引起社会的关注，让事件中的人与事得到重视和关注，进而得到合理解决，让人们了解事件的真相，揭发不为人知的内幕。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190824143000 +0800" stop="20190824150000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">美食攻略 Big Food   - EP 8</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) NUH has revolutionized their kitchen systems to cater to the needs of individual patients. Not an easy task when there are 1,000 people to feed three times a day! All allergy and dietary considerations must be met. It's about as complicated as it can get in the world of large scale catering. (重)(双声道-中/英).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190824150000 +0800" stop="20190824160000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">守护家族 (Dual Sound) Save The Family  - EP 3</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Xiuzi is upset when she sees Zhengshu humiliating Taizhen and not allowing him to enter the house. Xiuzi confronts Zhengshu, only to be insulted further. Xiuzi thus wants Taizhen to move back home with Yunjing and Xiubin. (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)秀子送小菜到太真家，刚好看到他被政淑羞辱，还被下令不得进屋。秀子恼羞成怒进屋找政淑理论，政淑却表现出一副看不起太真的样子。秀子回家后大声哭闹，跟家人说要太真带着老婆和孩子搬回家。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190824160000 +0800" stop="20190824170000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">守护家族 (Dual Sound) Save The Family  - EP 4</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Zhufeng develops diarrhoea after consuming a few servings of tonic. Rongxin goes to look for the salespeople, only to realise that they have been cheated. A group of elderly folks bring Meina to the police station when they suspect that she is in cahoots with the salespeople. (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)洙峰吃了补药后，腹泻不止。容心拿着补药到推销商那儿兴师问罪，才发现被骗了。许多老人家发现自己受骗后，以为美娜跟诈欺他们的推销员是一伙的，于是把美娜拉去警局。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190824170000 +0800" stop="20190824180000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">危情三日 3 Days  - EP 8</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Taiqing and Baoyuan bring the President away while Fengxiu pursues closely. In the process, Taiqing is forced to fire at Fengxiu in order to protect the President. However, the President affirms the result of the investigation conducted by the special prosecutor. This causes Taiqing to break down in tears. (PG-些许暴力画面)(重)(双声道-中/韩)为了确认真相，泰庆和宝媛先一步带走总统。奉秀对泰庆紧追不舍，泰庆为救总统不得已对奉秀开枪，却听到总统承认特检的调查属实。被真相震惊的泰庆洒泪崩溃。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190824180000 +0800" stop="20190824190000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">危情三日 3 Days  - EP 9</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Taiqing suspects that Fei Kang Group and the Chief of Staff are responsible for the murder of the Parliamentary Speaker. When Taiqing looks for the president of Cai Xin Group, he discovers that the confidential documents have been destroyed by fire. (PG-些许暴力画面)(重)(双声道-中/韩)权在延议长被杀的事让泰庆觉得飞康集团和秘书室长申奎镇有嫌疑。泰庆去找财信集团会长金道辰，却发现机密文件已被烧毁。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190824190000 +0800" stop="20190824210000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">无限歌谣季 Unlimited Song Season - EP 12</title>
    <desc lang="en">A variety show that allows the professional singer-songwriters to collaborate with non-professionals who were deemed to have potential to excel in the music industry. 该节目以音乐节为形式，让专业音乐人化身“无限唱作人"和非专业的“歌谣研修生"搭档创作新音乐.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190824210000 +0800" stop="20190824220000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">又是吳海英 Another Miss Oh  - EP 27</title>
    <desc lang="en">Taizhen glares angrily at Daojing, who just stepped out of his office. After some hesitation, Taizhen steps on the accelerator of his car and speeds towards Daojing who runs desperately for his life. Taizhen hits the brakes at the last moment, and his car stops just inches from Daojing.  (PG-些许性相关语)(双声道-中/韩)泰振在车里怒视着刚从办公室离开的道京。泰振踩上油门，开车冲向道京。正当车子就快撞上道京时，泰振及时刹车，车子差一点就撞上道京。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190824220000 +0800" stop="20190824230000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">又是吳海英 Another Miss Oh  - EP 28</title>
    <desc lang="en">On the marriage proposal day, Daojing sees the vision of his own death while standing at the entrance of the venue. Suddenly, a vehicle being pursued by a police car hits Daojing. Daojing suffers injury in the accident, but with the support of Haiying and his family and friends, he comes through the difficult period. The two eventually get married with the blessings of everyone.  (PG-部分画面令人不安)(大结局)(双声道-中/韩)在求婚当天，道京在场地门口等海英时，看到自己在车祸中将死去的一幕。突然，一辆被警车追逐的车把道京给撞飞。道京虽然还是遭遇了车祸，但在海英和所有家人朋友的陪伴下度过难关。两人最终也得到众人的祝福，顺利地完成婚礼。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190824230000 +0800" stop="20190824233000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻 News Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">A comprehensive half-hour news programme, NEWS TONIGHT provides viewers with important local, international and financial developments for the day. U频道《晚间新闻》，在半小时里除深入报道本地与国际要闻，还有详尽的财经新闻和体坛动态。世界局势与经济动脉，让大家轻松掌握。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190824233000 +0800" stop="20190825000000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">无限歌谣季 Unlimited Song Season - EP 12</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) A variety show that allows the professional singer-songwriters to collaborate with non-professionals who were deemed to have potential to excel in the music industry. (重)该节目以音乐节为形式，让专业音乐人化身“无限唱作人"和非专业的“歌谣研修生"搭档创作新音乐.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190825000000 +0800" stop="20190825013000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">无限歌谣季 Unlimited Song Season - EP 12</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) A variety show that allows the professional singer-songwriters to collaborate with non-professionals who were deemed to have potential to excel in the music industry. (重)该节目以音乐节为形式，让专业音乐人化身“无限唱作人"和非专业的“歌谣研修生"搭档创作新音乐.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190825013000 +0800" stop="20190825023000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">信号 Signal  - EP 16</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Haiying asks Caihan for help to find out the truth of the Renzhou Gang Rape Case which his brother, Shanyu, was involved in. Meanwhile, Caihan gets assigned to the case and heads to Renzhou to investigate... (PG-部分画面令人不安)(重)(双声道-中/韩)海英要材韩帮忙找出仁州女高中生案的真相，也就是他哥哥善宇所牵涉的案件。就在不久前，材韩被委派调查这宗非常案件，到仁州查明真相。。。。。。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190825023000 +0800" stop="20190825080000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190825080000 +0800" stop="20190825100000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">JML Home Shopping - Infomercial</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190825100000 +0800" stop="20190825120000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">梦想的声音 Sound Of My Dream S1 - EP 7</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Sound Of My Dream is a music program which invites Chinese pop singers to challenge musicians and other singers to pit their skills. Mentors and singers put in their best to show the essence of music, regardless of the outcome. (重)《梦想的声音》（原《声音的战争》）是一档由浙江卫视所打造的音乐节目，邀请到华语乐坛歌手面对面进行“歌艺过招”，导师与素人歌手抛开所有包袱，毫无保留的相互讨教，竭尽所能展现出音乐本质。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190825120000 +0800" stop="20190825123000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">搜密新加坡 Secret Singapore - EP 7</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Peifen visits a mysterious old building, tucked away at the Woodlands vicinity. Why are there heavily-grilled windows all around? What is the history behind this forlorn building? Later, Peifen stumbles on a peculiar garden with a tilted iron gate in the north-eastern corner of Singapore, as well as a kampong house in the middle of bustling Clementi Road. (重)(双声道-中/英).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190825123000 +0800" stop="20190825133000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">谁来晚餐2019 Guess Who 2019 - EP 13</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Celebrities will be invited to visit a family and join them for dinner. The family will have no idea who the celebrity will be beforehand. The invited celebrity will share his or her experience with the family through conversation during a meal. (重)(最后一集)“谁来晚餐" 是个时下颇为流行的实况电视节目. 每集节目都拜访一个家庭,并邀请他们的梦幻嘉宾上门共进晚餐.内容没有太多刻意的安排, 也许是小小梦想的完成, 也可能会看到名人卸下包装与身段之后的真情流露.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190825133000 +0800" stop="20190825140000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">寻找原之味 Food Old Days - EP 3</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Singapore is heralded as the Food Paradise and Singaporeans' favourite pastime includes searching out for the best hawker and local cuisines in every corner on the island. However, many traditional food fares are now on the brink of vanishing. Many of these stall owners are either old or retiring and found no one to succeed their businesses even though they may be thriving. (重)新加坡号称美食天堂，新加坡人最喜爱的休闲活动之一就是全岛搜寻最好吃的熟食档、到全岛各角落品尝本地美食。然而，随着时代进步、空间变迁，许多传统美食因为后继无人而渐渐消失，许多传统做法因为科技而渐渐失传。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190825140000 +0800" stop="20190825143000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">非一般递送 Special Delivery - EP 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Host Greta Georges is in Vietnam on a special delivery mission for World Vision, a humanitarian organization dedicated to tackling the root causes of poverty.  She has to buy a young cow, bring it for vaccination and insemination and then deliver the precious bovine. Waiting for Greta in Hung Yen province is a young woman who is shouldering the entire burden for her impoverished family comprising an aged father, a disabled husband; two malnourished children.  (重)六位主持人，各有不同的背景却身负同样的使命 – 递送非一般的物品给有需要的族群。他们的任务遍布亚洲偏僻各地，将考验他们的恒心、毅力与韧性。  秉持完成递送任务的坚定目标， 主持人将带领观众踏上一趟趟希望之旅，透过13集节目，让观众们感受《非一般的递送》送出的每一份快乐和感动。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190825143000 +0800" stop="20190825150000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">未来的食物工厂 Savouring the Future - EP 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) In this episode, Bjorn discovers how local food SMEs, Mr Bean and Hara, with the help of food labs, turn soy pulp - previously discarded - into innovative food products. (重)在《未来的食物工厂》，餐馆老板兼厨师沈观远将探讨新加坡中小型饮食企业运作和创新手法。  为了应对本地市场带来的挑战，中小型企业所采取的策略已超越自动化和研发新产品，迈向国际化的目标发展。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190825150000 +0800" stop="20190825160000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">守护家族 (Dual Sound) Save The Family  - EP 5</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Yiyuan proposes to supply cooked food to the hospital canteen. Haixiu and her fellow cooks object to the proposal as the move will directly affect their livelihoods. (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)艺苑以ONE'S食品代表的身份跟宇真任职的医院接洽，说要为医院提供优质的食物。艺苑参观餐厅，海秀和她的同事们因不了解医院为何有厨师还要接受ONE'S食品的半现成食物，与艺苑起口角。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190825160000 +0800" stop="20190825170000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">守护家族 (Dual Sound) Save The Family  - EP 6</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Wancai is admitted to the neighbourhood hospital when he meets with a traffic accident. It is then that he and Xiuzi discover that Yuzhen is no longer working at the university hospital. Wancai and Xiuzi are devastated as they have pinned all their hopes on Yuzhen. (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)万才发生车祸，从而发现宇真已经不在大学医院工作了。万才和秀子把一切希望寄托在宇真身上，发现他在小医院上班，伤心不已。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190825170000 +0800" stop="20190825180000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">危情三日 3 Days  - EP 10</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) The President hopes Taiqing can stay and protect him. However, the death of Fengxiu and loss of faith lead Taiqing to tender his resignation. Kuizhen dismisses the other officers and tries to get the Prime Minister to stand on the same side of the fence. (PG-些许暴力画面)(重)(双声道-中/韩)总统希望泰庆可以留下来保护自己，但奉秀的死和信念的迷失早已让泰庆失去自信，决定辞去警卫员一职。奎镇开始私下辞退其他官员并拉拢总理。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190825180000 +0800" stop="20190825190000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">危情三日 3 Days  - EP 11</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Taiqing decodes the encrypted document left behind by his father and looks for the witness, Major Li Zhekui. Meanwhile, Daochen tries to stop Li from attending the press conference. (PG-些许暴力画面)(重)(双声道-中/韩)在宝媛的影响下，泰庆破解了父亲的加密文件，并寻找证人李哲奎少佐。此时道辰极力阻止哲奎出席记者招待会。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190825190000 +0800" stop="20190825210000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">梦想的声音 3 Sound Of My Dream S3 - EP 3</title>
    <desc lang="en">A music variety where a number of talented singers, amateur or otherwise are given the chance to "challenge" a celebrity tutor by singing one of the celebrity's songs. In exchange, the celebrity is assigned one of four randomly selected songs and has three hours to come up with a cover performance of this song.  与上季相同，基本模式为星素挑战，由追梦歌手对导师发起讨教（挑战）。但在第三季开始，选歌模式已经更换为第一季的模式，可是选择权是由参赛者说“开始”的时候，只要喊“停”，那一首歌曲就是讨教老师要唱的歌。和第一季不一样的是，每一首歌都有关键词。如果进行第二轮讨教，是没有任何的关键词。时间也从之前的6个小时改成3个小时。据华少声称，如果“惊”曲榜里的歌曲原唱者是导师的话，讨教歌手若是选择原唱者导师，将会带来的难度和风险更大，最终导致讨教失败。这一季的歌手包括林俊杰，王嘉尔，胡彦斌，张靓颖，谭维维 等。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190825210000 +0800" stop="20190825220000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">我的契约老公吴先生 My Contracted Husband, Mr Oh  - EP 1</title>
    <desc lang="en">Jingshu asks Shengzhu out and tells her that director Hong, knowing that she will only report for work at the TV station three weeks later, wants her to help produce a two episodes special documentary for the founding of his company. Shengzhu initially wanted to turn down the job and enjoy a long break. However, she accepts the challenge after finding out that she is to film the grandson of the legendary master of gayageum, Wu He. She decides to look for Wu He in the mountains with the address provided by director Hong.  (PG)(首播)(双声道-中/韩)景淑约胜珠见面告诉她洪代表知道她3周后才去电视台工作，要找她帮他公司制作2 集创社特辑的传统记录片。胜珠原想推掉放大假，但听是要拍摄传说中远离俗世的伽耶琴名匠的孙子吴赫，便觉得很有挑战性。她决定拿着洪代表给的地址去山里寻找那名匠后人吴赫….</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190825220000 +0800" stop="20190825230000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">我的契约老公吴先生 My Contracted Husband, Mr Oh  - EP 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Shengzhu's brother Shengtai and mother, unbeknownst to Shengzhu, surreptitiously visit the piece of mountain land which Shengzhu's aunt has given to her. They plan to chase the residents of the villagers out from there and start a resort venture. When Zuodou learns about this and finds out that Shengzhu is the landlord, he immediately leaves the mountains and looks for Shengzhu to persuade her to let him continue staying there. Fortuitously, he saves Shengzhu from a masked man trying to kill her. (PG-部分画面令人不安)(双声道-中/韩)胜珠的弟弟胜泰与妈妈瞒着胜珠，偷偷跑去看姑姑送给胜珠的山地。他们打算赶走住在山里的村民，以做度假村的投资。当作斗知道这个消息和得知地主是胜珠后，立刻下山去找胜珠商量让他继续居住的事，却凑巧救了差点遭蒙面男人杀害的胜珠。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190825230000 +0800" stop="20190825233000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻 News Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">A comprehensive half-hour news programme, NEWS TONIGHT provides viewers with important local, international and financial developments for the day. U频道《晚间新闻》，在半小时里除深入报道本地与国际要闻，还有详尽的财经新闻和体坛动态。世界局势与经济动脉，让大家轻松掌握。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190825233000 +0800" stop="20190826000000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">梦想的声音 3 Sound Of My Dream S3 - EP 3</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) A music variety where a number of talented singers, amateur or otherwise are given the chance to "challenge" a celebrity tutor by singing one of the celebrity's songs. In exchange, the celebrity is assigned one of four randomly selected songs and has three hours to come up with a cover performance of this song.  (重)与上季相同，基本模式为星素挑战，由追梦歌手对导师发起讨教（挑战）。但在第三季开始，选歌模式已经更换为第一季的模式，可是选择权是由参赛者说“开始”的时候，只要喊“停”，那一首歌曲就是讨教老师要唱的歌。和第一季不一样的是，每一首歌都有关键词。如果进行第二轮讨教，是没有任何的关键词。时间也从之前的6个小时改成3个小时。据华少声称，如果“惊”曲榜里的歌曲原唱者是导师的话，讨教歌手若是选择原唱者导师，将会带来的难度和风险更大，最终导致讨教失败。这一季的歌手包括林俊杰，王嘉尔，胡彦斌，张靓颖，谭维维 等。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190826000000 +0800" stop="20190826013000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">梦想的声音 3 Sound Of My Dream S3 - EP 3</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) A music variety where a number of talented singers, amateur or otherwise are given the chance to "challenge" a celebrity tutor by singing one of the celebrity's songs. In exchange, the celebrity is assigned one of four randomly selected songs and has three hours to come up with a cover performance of this song.  (重)与上季相同，基本模式为星素挑战，由追梦歌手对导师发起讨教（挑战）。但在第三季开始，选歌模式已经更换为第一季的模式，可是选择权是由参赛者说“开始”的时候，只要喊“停”，那一首歌曲就是讨教老师要唱的歌。和第一季不一样的是，每一首歌都有关键词。如果进行第二轮讨教，是没有任何的关键词。时间也从之前的6个小时改成3个小时。据华少声称，如果“惊”曲榜里的歌曲原唱者是导师的话，讨教歌手若是选择原唱者导师，将会带来的难度和风险更大，最终导致讨教失败。这一季的歌手包括林俊杰，王嘉尔，胡彦斌，张靓颖，谭维维 等。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190826013000 +0800" stop="20190826023000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">信号 Signal  - EP 17</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Zhishou decides to tell Haiying the truth about the Renzhou high school rape case and asks Haiying to meet him in front of the Renzhou Hospital. However, he is dead by the time Haiying arrives. Xiuxian is shocked and saddened after learning that Caihan was killed by Zhishou many years ago. (PG-部分画面令人不安)(重)(双声道-中/韩)治守打电话给海英要告诉他当年仁州女高中生案件的真相，约了他在仁州医院前见面。可是当海英到达时，发现治守已遭人杀害。当秀贤得知治守当年亲手杀了材韩一事后，感到十分惊讶和难过。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190826023000 +0800" stop="20190826110000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190826110000 +0800" stop="20190826150000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">JML Home Shopping - Infomercial</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190826150000 +0800" stop="20190826160000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">小当家 Little Maestros - EP 9</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Abandoned at birth, Ding Yan was adopted 12 years ago. Her foster father found work in another town, leaving her as a stay-at-home child to shoulder the task to care for her ill grandparents. Why is she willing to take up such chores and farm work, giving her all for a family without blood relation? (重)丁燕是一名弃婴，12年前，她被人收养。但养父在她很小的时候就外出打工，她成了留守儿童，在家中负起照顾生病的爷爷和奶奶的责任。是什么令她愿意承担起所有的家务和农活，撑起一个毫无血缘关系的家呢？.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190826160000 +0800" stop="20190826170000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">金星火星大不同 Mars Vs Venus - EP 9</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Why are Singaporean women not marriage material? Are Singaporean men simply not good enough? Formal TV presenter Diana Ser joins the panel this week and shares her thoughts on this juicy topic. What will the Martians do to protect their pride and dignity? Let's find out! (重)久违了的美丽人妻徐秀盈首次上节目！身为新加坡女人，她是否认为新加坡女人嫁不出全都是受新加坡男人牵连？郑斌辉和苏梽诚要如何反驳和争辩，为新加坡男人保住立场！看了这集，你会对新加坡女人和男人有不同的看法！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190826170000 +0800" stop="20190826180000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">我女婿的女人 Marrying My Daughter Twice  - EP 28</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Yuzhi introduces Xiantai to a Mr Huang who orders 3000 jackets from Xiantai. Unexpectedly, Mr Huang disappears without making payment after receiving the goods. Xiantai is suspected of receiving bribes from Mr Huang. Yinghao wants Xiantai to resign and take responsibility of the losses suffered by the company. (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)宇植在载永的指使下安排一位假社长向贤泰订购三千套团体服。该社长在收货后失联，令KP集团收不到付款，贤泰还被闭路电视拍到疑似收取贿赂的画面。英鎬要贤泰辞职，为公司蒙受的损失负责。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190826180000 +0800" stop="20190826190000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">医疗船 Hospital Ship  - EP 12</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Cui Yingen confides to Guo Xian that she has been diagnosed with acute leukaemia and left with two years life. She hopes Guo Xian can take care of her. Enzai gets anxious learning that her brother, Yuzai, has been injured in a site accident.  (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)崔英恩告诉郭贤她患了急性骨髓性白血病，可能只有两年的命，希望郭贤这段时间能照顾她。恩在得知弟弟宇在在地盘现场受了伤，大感焦急。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190826190000 +0800" stop="20190826200000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">黄金光辉的人生 My Golden Life  - EP 13</title>
    <desc lang="en">Zhi-an skips a lesson to rush to Zhixiu's side when she finds out that Zhixiu is drunk. Mingxi is displeased with Zhi-an's behaviour and orders for everything that can remind Zhi-an of the Xus to be thrown away.  (PG)(双声道-中/韩)知安拨电给知秀时发现知秀喝醉了，于是立刻翘课赶到知秀的身边。明熙大为不悦，要闵部长把能够勾起知安对徐家的眷恋的物品一律丢掉，令知安难过不已。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190826200000 +0800" stop="20190826210000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">黄金光辉的人生 My Golden Life  - EP 14</title>
    <desc lang="en">Zhi-an attempts to climb over the wall to retrieve her belongings that have been thrown away by Mingxi. Daojing stops her. He returns Zhi-an's prized wood figurines to her and also brings her out for a drink. Daojing's thoughtfulness enables Zhi-an to change her impression of him.  (PG)(双声道-中/韩)知安尝试爬墙到屋外出去找被明熙丢掉的东西，却被道京逮个正着。道京把知安的木雕还给她，还带知安去喝啤酒。两人的关系因此改善。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190826210000 +0800" stop="20190826214000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">北京到莫斯科 Beijing To Moscow  - EP 10</title>
    <desc lang="en">After finding Mei Ling, she reveals that she met Kloudiia in church. Kloudiia had turned to the church to help cope with her grief of losing An Ran and the reason for Kloudiia's suicide attempt triggered Kai Xiang's memories to flood back in. While Kai Xiang was preparing for his wedding, An Ran had a terrible accident that left him fighting for his life. At a loss of what to do, Kloudiia begged Kai Xiang to return to Moscow to see his son.  (PG)美玲是Kloudiia在教会认识的好友，在她初遇Kloudiia时，Kloudiia正处于崩溃的边缘。是她一直陪伴Kloudiia，帮她走出人生低谷。原来Kloudiia还活着，不过孩子已经不在了！当时Kloudiia是因为突如其来的丧子之痛才崩溃选择自杀。Kloudiia自杀丧子的真相，刺激了凯翔，也揭开了他逃婚的谜底。原来凯翔和筱琦筹备婚礼时，安然却遇上严重意外，危在旦夕。慌张失措的Kloudiia恳求凯翔到莫斯科一趟，见他们的孩子安然最后一面。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190826214000 +0800" stop="20190826220000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">混口饭吃而已 Hear My Thoughts - EP 10</title>
    <desc lang="en">Familiar real-life scenarios with hilarious caricature, Hear My Thoughts brings to attention the bottled-up sentiments of people at their workplace. 幽默短片《混口饭吃而已》，以逗趣的方式叙述各行各业的酸甜苦辣！打工仔的内心喊话及苦衷——只有自己最清楚，真相也绝非你所能想象！演员阵容包括：田铭耀、鐘琴、王智荟、胡佳嬑、坤华、罗翊绮及林茜茜，还有客串嘉宾周崇庆、权怡凤、朱厚任等。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190826220000 +0800" stop="20190826230000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">你那边怎样.我这边OK  - 台湾篇 All Is Well - Taiwan - EP 1</title>
    <desc lang="en">A cargo ship sailed quietly along the offshore of The Philippines. A crew member, Ma Dong Bao, smuggled people up the ship and killed the rest of the members, leaving only Cai Fu Lai, the chef, to live. Cai Fu Lai, Eric and Dong Huang are good friends who grew up together. Eric faked his education credentials to work at Singapore's Teng Sheng Bank, but his act gets exposed by Linda, the director, and is threatened by her.  (PG-些许暴力画面)(首播)菲律宾外海，货船“孝亲号”安静地航行。船员马东宝暗中带人上船，杀死其他船员，只留下厨师蔡富莱一个活口。蔡富莱与Eric、栋煌是一起长大的好友。Eric假造学历进入新加坡腾升银行工作，被主管Linda识破而威胁他。Eric被逼下，答应网友Justin邀请，到台湾参加提款测试……。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190826230000 +0800" stop="20190826233000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻 News Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">A comprehensive half-hour news programme, NEWS TONIGHT provides viewers with important local, international and financial developments for the day. U频道《晚间新闻》，在半小时里除深入报道本地与国际要闻，还有详尽的财经新闻和体坛动态。世界局势与经济动脉，让大家轻松掌握。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190826233000 +0800" stop="20190827000000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">北京到莫斯科 Beijing To Moscow  - EP 10</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) After finding Mei Ling, she reveals that she met Kloudiia in church. Kloudiia had turned to the church to help cope with her grief of losing An Ran and the reason for Kloudiia's suicide attempt triggered Kai Xiang's memories to flood back in. While Kai Xiang was preparing for his wedding, An Ran had a terrible accident that left him fighting for his life. At a loss of what to do, Kloudiia begged Kai Xiang to return to Moscow to see his son.  (PG)(重)美玲是Kloudiia在教会认识的好友，在她初遇Kloudiia时，Kloudiia正处于崩溃的边缘。是她一直陪伴Kloudiia，帮她走出人生低谷。原来Kloudiia还活着，不过孩子已经不在了！当时Kloudiia是因为突如其来的丧子之痛才崩溃选择自杀。Kloudiia自杀丧子的真相，刺激了凯翔，也揭开了他逃婚的谜底。原来凯翔和筱琦筹备婚礼时，安然却遇上严重意外，危在旦夕。慌张失措的Kloudiia恳求凯翔到莫斯科一趟，见他们的孩子安然最后一面。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190827000000 +0800" stop="20190827001000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">北京到莫斯科 Beijing To Moscow  - EP 10</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) After finding Mei Ling, she reveals that she met Kloudiia in church. Kloudiia had turned to the church to help cope with her grief of losing An Ran and the reason for Kloudiia's suicide attempt triggered Kai Xiang's memories to flood back in. While Kai Xiang was preparing for his wedding, An Ran had a terrible accident that left him fighting for his life. At a loss of what to do, Kloudiia begged Kai Xiang to return to Moscow to see his son.  (PG)(重)美玲是Kloudiia在教会认识的好友，在她初遇Kloudiia时，Kloudiia正处于崩溃的边缘。是她一直陪伴Kloudiia，帮她走出人生低谷。原来Kloudiia还活着，不过孩子已经不在了！当时Kloudiia是因为突如其来的丧子之痛才崩溃选择自杀。Kloudiia自杀丧子的真相，刺激了凯翔，也揭开了他逃婚的谜底。原来凯翔和筱琦筹备婚礼时，安然却遇上严重意外，危在旦夕。慌张失措的Kloudiia恳求凯翔到莫斯科一趟，见他们的孩子安然最后一面。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190827001000 +0800" stop="20190827003000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">混口饭吃而已 Hear My Thoughts - EP 10</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Familiar real-life scenarios with hilarious caricature, Hear My Thoughts brings to attention the bottled-up sentiments of people at their workplace. (重)幽默短片《混口饭吃而已》，以逗趣的方式叙述各行各业的酸甜苦辣！打工仔的内心喊话及苦衷——只有自己最清楚，真相也绝非你所能想象！演员阵容包括：田铭耀、鐘琴、王智荟、胡佳嬑、坤华、罗翊绮及林茜茜，还有客串嘉宾周崇庆、权怡凤、朱厚任等。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190827003000 +0800" stop="20190827013000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">黄金光辉的人生 My Golden Life  - EP 13</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Zhi-an skips a lesson to rush to Zhixiu's side when she finds out that Zhixiu is drunk. Mingxi is displeased with Zhi-an's behaviour and orders for everything that can remind Zhi-an of the Xus to be thrown away.  (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)知安拨电给知秀时发现知秀喝醉了，于是立刻翘课赶到知秀的身边。明熙大为不悦，要闵部长把能够勾起知安对徐家的眷恋的物品一律丢掉，令知安难过不已。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190827013000 +0800" stop="20190827023000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">黄金光辉的人生 My Golden Life  - EP 14</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Zhi-an attempts to climb over the wall to retrieve her belongings that have been thrown away by Mingxi. Daojing stops her. He returns Zhi-an's prized wood figurines to her and also brings her out for a drink. Daojing's thoughtfulness enables Zhi-an to change her impression of him.  (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)知安尝试爬墙到屋外出去找被明熙丢掉的东西，却被道京逮个正着。道京把知安的木雕还给她，还带知安去喝啤酒。两人的关系因此改善。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190827023000 +0800" stop="20190827110000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190827110000 +0800" stop="20190827150000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">JML Home Shopping - Infomercial</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190827150000 +0800" stop="20190827160000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">Fresh!新登场 – 佩佩 Fresh Takes - Pei Pei</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) "Fresh Takes" is a series of 10 local short films directed and produced by Mediacorp artistes Bryan Wong, Romeo Tan, Shane Pow, Priscelia Chan, Joanne Peh and Ian Fang, as well as production teams from Mediacorp Chinese Drama, Studiomonki, Wawa Pictures and August Pictures. (PG)(重)一位深藏在记忆中的女儿，明明是最亲的人，却无法释出关心的一面。女儿的心永远漂浮不定，思念着家乡却没有勇气回到父亲身旁了。佩佩离开乌敏岛到新加坡独自生活，认识了性感美女Tracy和豪爽帅气的阿哲三人成为好朋友。在两人的影响下，佩佩靠自己的才华慢慢成为网红。一段裸露影片在网络中流传，三人的关系进而发生巨大的变化。正寿等不到回家吃饭的女儿，决定与女儿的好友阿健一起到新加坡寻找佩佩，才发现记忆中最亲近的女儿已经不是自己想象中的样子，女儿在新加坡遭遇的事情成为父亲心里最痛的那根刺。最后，父亲决定回到家乡，等待女儿回来，然而佩佩是否会回到父亲的身边呢？.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190827160000 +0800" stop="20190827170000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">百味人生 Food Of Life - EP 13</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Life and death is a natural cycle of life. People pay last respect to the deceased and express their loss through funeral rituals. Funeral is the most serious event in life and each ethnic groups has their own unique funeral customs and food culture. Food brings the people closer in mourning period. (重)(最后一集)生死循环，生命的自然定律。人们借着丧礼给离世的人最后的敬礼。丧礼是人生中最为严肃的礼仪，让亲友表达对死者的思念。各民族都有其独特的丧葬文化，丧葬活动有饮食文化的介入，同吃共食拉近了人们的心理距离。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190827170000 +0800" stop="20190827180000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">我女婿的女人 Marrying My Daughter Twice  - EP 29</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Zaiyong instructs Mr Huang to release the jackets at low prices, leading franchisees to ask KP Group for an explanation. KP Group faces its greatest crisis since the start of its operations. Xiantai is arrested for dereliction of duty. (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)载永指使冒牌社长将之前到手的外套以低价抛出市面，令总公司难以向加盟店的社长们交待。 KP集团面临创业以来最大的危机。贤泰以渎职罪被KP集团提告。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190827180000 +0800" stop="20190827190000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">医疗船 Hospital Ship  - EP 13</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Enzai's father requests Guo Xian to forge his medical report in order to claim his insurance. Enzai overheard and reprimanded her father. (PG-部分画面令人不安)(重)(双声道-中/韩)恩在的父亲叫郭贤在他的医诊报告上作假，好让他领到保险金，此时恩在听到了出言阻止。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190827190000 +0800" stop="20190827200000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">黄金光辉的人生 My Golden Life  - EP 15</title>
    <desc lang="en">Xiuya goes for a makeover in an attempt to forget Zhitai. Her new look attracts the attention of a lawyer, but Xiuya dismisses him as she is constantly reminded of Zhitai. (PG)(双声道-中/韩)秀雅为了忘了知泰，到美容院改头换面一番，成功被一名帅气的律师搭讪，却因为想到知泰而拒绝律师的追求。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190827200000 +0800" stop="20190827210000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">黄金光辉的人生 My Golden Life  - EP 16</title>
    <desc lang="en">Mingxi goes to an art gallery with a group of socialites. One of them reveals that Mingxi has found her long-lost daughter. Mingxi has no choice but to ask Zhi-an to show up at the art gallery when the socialites demand to see her. Zhi-an impresses everyone with her art knowledge. (PG)(双声道-中/韩)明熙与太太们一起到美术馆赏画，出乎意料地被一位名媛揭穿她已经找到女儿的事。太太们要求与知安见面，明熙骑虎难下，要知安立刻出席聚会。知安以出色的美术知识令在场的太太们对她刮目相看。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190827210000 +0800" stop="20190827220000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">笔墨间的飨宴 A Literary Feast - EP 1</title>
    <desc lang="en">'A Literary Feast' features delectable dishes from renowned literary novels, and explores the hidden stories behind each dish. Discover the art of cuisine behind the traditional flavours of these impeccable legendary dishes. (首播)《笔墨间的飨宴》节目将呈现各地不同名著、地方传说相关的种种美食。在挑动观众味蕾的同时，探讨各地传说美食背后的人文故事与饮食文化，进一步了解吃的艺术。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190827220000 +0800" stop="20190827230000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">你那边怎样.我这边OK  - 台湾篇 All Is Well - Taiwan - EP 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Eric and Dong Huang unknowingly get involved in an ATM heist after participating in the test. Justin deceives Eric about the program being bought by a security company and they would pay him, putting Eric at ease. Teng Sheng Bank found that the ATM was attacked by hackers and 80 million was "robbed". Vice president Guo Yan Feng ordered the police and media to keep it a secret, however, the news still spread online, and rookie reporter Liu Wei Yun finds out about the incident. (PG)Eric、栋煌因参加测试而卷入提款机盗领案，却不自知。Justin欺骗Eric有关程序已被一资安公司买下，并付款给他，Eric感放心。腾升银行发现提款机被骇客攻击，盗领8千万，副总裁郭延丰下令对警方和媒体保密，然而网路上还是传出风声，被菜鸟记者刘维芸发现。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190827230000 +0800" stop="20190827233000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻 News Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">A comprehensive half-hour news programme, NEWS TONIGHT provides viewers with important local, international and financial developments for the day. U频道《晚间新闻》，在半小时里除深入报道本地与国际要闻，还有详尽的财经新闻和体坛动态。世界局势与经济动脉，让大家轻松掌握。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190827233000 +0800" stop="20190828000000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">笔墨间的飨宴 A Literary Feast - EP 1</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) 'A Literary Feast' features delectable dishes from renowned literary novels, and explores the hidden stories behind each dish. Discover the art of cuisine behind the traditional flavours of these impeccable legendary dishes. (重)《笔墨间的飨宴》节目将呈现各地不同名著、地方传说相关的种种美食。在挑动观众味蕾的同时，探讨各地传说美食背后的人文故事与饮食文化，进一步了解吃的艺术。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190828000000 +0800" stop="20190828003000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">笔墨间的飨宴 A Literary Feast - EP 1</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) 'A Literary Feast' features delectable dishes from renowned literary novels, and explores the hidden stories behind each dish. Discover the art of cuisine behind the traditional flavours of these impeccable legendary dishes. (重)《笔墨间的飨宴》节目将呈现各地不同名著、地方传说相关的种种美食。在挑动观众味蕾的同时，探讨各地传说美食背后的人文故事与饮食文化，进一步了解吃的艺术。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190828003000 +0800" stop="20190828013000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">黄金光辉的人生 My Golden Life  - EP 15</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Xiuya goes for a makeover in an attempt to forget Zhitai. Her new look attracts the attention of a lawyer, but Xiuya dismisses him as she is constantly reminded of Zhitai. (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)秀雅为了忘了知泰，到美容院改头换面一番，成功被一名帅气的律师搭讪，却因为想到知泰而拒绝律师的追求。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190828013000 +0800" stop="20190828023000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">黄金光辉的人生 My Golden Life  - EP 16</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Mingxi goes to an art gallery with a group of socialites. One of them reveals that Mingxi has found her long-lost daughter. Mingxi has no choice but to ask Zhi-an to show up at the art gallery when the socialites demand to see her. Zhi-an impresses everyone with her art knowledge. (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)明熙与太太们一起到美术馆赏画，出乎意料地被一位名媛揭穿她已经找到女儿的事。太太们要求与知安见面，明熙骑虎难下，要知安立刻出席聚会。知安以出色的美术知识令在场的太太们对她刮目相看。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190828023000 +0800" stop="20190828110000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190828110000 +0800" stop="20190828150000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">JML Home Shopping - Infomercial</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190828150000 +0800" stop="20190828160000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">创! (PG) Start Up! - EP 12</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Jessie presents strong evidence to prove that Graffiti copied Enzo's Application, "Hands". These materials had belonged to Xuan's dad and were in Xuan's possession, stored in her wooden box. Sun Shao found out that Doobie is meeting Jessie, in secret! (PG)(重)Jessie提出有力的证据，证明殷萱的Graffiti的确是抄袭Hand！的。这其中的证据，包括了设计蓝图、专利申请书。殷萱发现这些都是属于殷堂的，全部都是放在木制盒子里的。Graffiti要怎么化险为意？ 孙少发现Doobie与Jessie见面，愕然神色！.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190828160000 +0800" stop="20190828170000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">一人行。暖人心 Going Miles, Spreading Smiles - EP 6</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) It all began in 2007, when Annie came across news articles about the internal conflicts in Myanmar. She felt deeply for the homeless and innocent kids and wanted to lend a helping hand. That was when she decided to make a trip to Myanmar. (重)2007年看了缅甸内战的新闻，得知数以万计的儿童流离失所，义工Annie决定"一人行"，实地探访当地孤儿院，希望尽自己微薄的力量、给予协助。就这样，她展开了她的公益人生，每年6月和12月学校假期时，都会抽空到缅甸举办夏令营，教育孩子英文、手工艺和正确的生活习惯。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190828170000 +0800" stop="20190828180000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">我女婿的女人 Marrying My Daughter Twice  - EP 30</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Xiuqing agrees to marry Zaiyong in exchange for Xiantai's release. Xiantai rushes to ask Xiuqing for an explanation when he receives news of her impending wedding. Xiuqing says she has got tired of him. (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)秀卿为了让贤泰尽早获释，答应跟载永结婚。贤泰听说秀卿的婚讯，匆匆忙忙地找秀卿问个明白。秀卿表现得很镇定，说跟贤泰在一起很辛苦，之前只是在追求刺激感。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190828180000 +0800" stop="20190828190000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">医疗船 Hospital Ship  - EP 14</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Guo Xian is worried when Yingen gives up her chemo treatment. Yingen warns Enzai to stay away from Guo Xian, however Enzai confronts Yingen for faking illness to win back Guo Xian's love. (PG-部分画面令人不安)(重)(双声道-中/韩)郭贤得知英恩想放弃治疗而担心不已. 英恩向恩在宣言，叫她别再缠着郭贤; 恩在反揭穿英恩用患病的理由欺骗郭贤。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190828190000 +0800" stop="20190828200000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">黄金光辉的人生 My Golden Life  - EP 17</title>
    <desc lang="en">Zhi-an suspects that she is not the real Enshi. She is relieved when Min assures her that her identity has been confirmed by a paternity test.  (PG)(双声道-中/韩)知安怀疑自己不是真正的恩石，但闵部长说已经做过亲子鉴定，知安于是放心不少。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190828200000 +0800" stop="20190828210000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">黄金光辉的人生 My Golden Life  - EP 18</title>
    <desc lang="en">Zhi-an compares an old photo of Enshi with that of the deceased twin and realises that Zhixiu is the real Enshi.  (PG)(双声道-中/韩)知安拿着恩石当年失踪的旧剪报回家跟去世的双胞胎的照片做比对，证实当年失踪的孩子是知秀，不是她。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190828210000 +0800" stop="20190828213000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">非一般递送 Special Delivery - EP 3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Two years after a catastrophic earthquake struck Nepal, there are many who continue to live with the repercussions of the seismic disaster. Homes have not been fully rebuilt leaving victims without shelter, and schools are still in the process of being repaired. Host Paul Foster hooks up with his Nepalese friends to undertake a tough, dangerous and exhilarating 14-hour drive up the mountains in a special delivery of masonry that will help rebuild schools. 六位主持人，各有不同的背景却身负同样的使命 – 递送非一般的物品给有需要的族群。他们的任务遍布亚洲偏僻各地，将考验他们的恒心、毅力与韧性。  秉持完成递送任务的坚定目标， 主持人将带领观众踏上一趟趟希望之旅，透过13集节目，让观众们感受《非一般的递送》送出的每一份快乐和感动。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190828213000 +0800" stop="20190828220000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">未来的食物工厂 Savouring the Future - EP 3</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this episode, Bjorn meets the driving forces behind Mr Popiah and Health Food Matters, the people who are innovating their food products, all for a specific but growing group of consumers. 在《未来的食物工厂》，餐馆老板兼厨师沈观远将探讨新加坡中小型饮食企业运作和创新手法。  为了应对本地市场带来的挑战，中小型企业所采取的策略已超越自动化和研发新产品，迈向国际化的目标发展。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190828220000 +0800" stop="20190828230000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">你那边怎样.我这边OK  - 台湾篇 All is Well - Taiwan - EP 3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Teng Sheng Bank did not report the case. Wei Yun's cousin, Dong Jie is a police officer. He asked Wei Yun to release the news that Teng Sheng Bank's ATM has been robbed, wanting to use the pressure of public opinion to force the bank to report the case, so that the police is able to commence an official investigation. Wei Yun happily agrees. The Taiwan police officially formed an ATM hacking case team. Eric sees the news reports on the hacking case and has a bad feeling about it.  (PG)腾升银行没有报案，维芸的堂哥东杰是警察，要求维芸发布腾升银行提款机被盗领的新闻，欲以舆论压力逼银行报案，让警方有立场立案调查，维芸乐得照做。台湾警方正式成立ATM盗领案专案小组。Eric看见盗领案新闻，感觉大事不妙。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190828230000 +0800" stop="20190828233000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻 News Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">A comprehensive half-hour news programme, NEWS TONIGHT provides viewers with important local, international and financial developments for the day. U频道《晚间新闻》，在半小时里除深入报道本地与国际要闻，还有详尽的财经新闻和体坛动态。世界局势与经济动脉，让大家轻松掌握。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190828233000 +0800" stop="20190829000000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">非一般递送 Special Delivery - EP 3</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Two years after a catastrophic earthquake struck Nepal, there are many who continue to live with the repercussions of the seismic disaster. Homes have not been fully rebuilt leaving victims without shelter, and schools are still in the process of being repaired. Host Paul Foster hooks up with his Nepalese friends to undertake a tough, dangerous and exhilarating 14-hour drive up the mountains in a special delivery of masonry that will help rebuild schools. (重)六位主持人，各有不同的背景却身负同样的使命 – 递送非一般的物品给有需要的族群。他们的任务遍布亚洲偏僻各地，将考验他们的恒心、毅力与韧性。  秉持完成递送任务的坚定目标， 主持人将带领观众踏上一趟趟希望之旅，透过13集节目，让观众们感受《非一般的递送》送出的每一份快乐和感动。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190829000000 +0800" stop="20190829003000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">未来的食物工厂 Savouring the Future - EP 3</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) In this episode, Bjorn meets the driving forces behind Mr Popiah and Health Food Matters, the people who are innovating their food products, all for a specific but growing group of consumers.  (重)在《未来的食物工厂》，餐馆老板兼厨师沈观远将探讨新加坡中小型饮食企业运作和创新手法。  为了应对本地市场带来的挑战，中小型企业所采取的策略已超越自动化和研发新产品，迈向国际化的目标发展。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190829003000 +0800" stop="20190829013000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">黄金光辉的人生 My Golden Life  - EP 17</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Zhi-an suspects that she is not the real Enshi. She is relieved when Min assures her that her identity has been confirmed by a paternity test.  (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)知安怀疑自己不是真正的恩石，但闵部长说已经做过亲子鉴定，知安于是放心不少。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190829013000 +0800" stop="20190829023000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">黄金光辉的人生 My Golden Life  - EP 18</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Zhi-an compares an old photo of Enshi with that of the deceased twin and realises that Zhixiu is the real Enshi.  (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)知安拿着恩石当年失踪的旧剪报回家跟去世的双胞胎的照片做比对，证实当年失踪的孩子是知秀，不是她。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190829023000 +0800" stop="20190829110000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">End of Transmission</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190829110000 +0800" stop="20190829150000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">JML Home Shopping - Infomercial</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190829150000 +0800" stop="20190829160000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">买卖 Business As Usual - EP 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Can money buy everything? From hair, manure to time, if someone sees its value, anything can be a commodity. "Business As Usual" explores the unique trades of the world, uncovering why they have emerged and revealing how they closely intertwine with societal changes and human nature. (重)母乳是婴儿成长最天然的营养品，而美国是少数可合法售卖母乳的国家，有些母亲通过母乳银行购买母乳，有些母亲则通过网站售卖自己的母乳。为了确保新鲜母乳能被及时运送，一群义务女性骑士自告奋勇帮忙运送，也有妈妈将母乳制成饰品出售。这一集看看美国纽约的母乳买卖如何进行？.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190829160000 +0800" stop="20190829163000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">探索食材 The Food Detectives 3   - EP 6</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) The new season of "The Food Detectives" continues the culinary exploration of the foods we eat and more. Host Nikki Muller, will debunk the myths, delve into the unknowns and provide useful information to help us make informed choices for the meals we enjoy and how they fit into our lifestyles. (重)(双声道-中/英).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190829163000 +0800" stop="20190829170000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">传说中的料理 II Legendary Cuisines 2 - EP 7</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Do you know that Genghis Khan must have grilled skewered mutton before he leaves for the battlefield? Or how is the Dowager Chrysanthemum Hot Pot related to Empress Cixi? The new season of Legendary Cuisines has the answers. (重)你尝过鸳鸯鸡粥吗？知道梅兰芳在登台前必吃的心是什么吗？太后菊花锅和慈禧太后有什么关系？新系列的《传说中的料理》将为你解答。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190829170000 +0800" stop="20190829180000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">我女婿的女人 Marrying My Daughter Twice  - EP 31</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Yijun and Xiantai finally find Mr Huang and also locate a recorded conversation between Mr Huang and Zaiyong in Mr Huang's phone. Xiantai hears from Xiaoxun that Xiuqing agreed to marry Xiantai for the sake of him and Xiaoxun. Xiantai rushes to the wedding venue and brings Xiuqing away. (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)益俊和贤泰终于找到黄社长，还在他的电话里听到他与载永的通话录音。载永和秀卿结婚当天，贤泰从小勋的口中听说秀卿是为了他们父子俩才答应嫁给载永的。贤泰赶往婚礼现场抢新娘。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190829180000 +0800" stop="20190829190000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">医疗船 Hospital Ship  - EP 15</title>
    <desc lang="en">(R) Enzai makes a plea to Dr Jin to operate on his father but the latter rejected. Enzai decides to operate on his father personally. The team members are willing to give her a helping hand.  (PG)(重)(双声道-中/韩)恩在拜托金道勋医生替父亲做手术，但金医生以病患太多为由推辞. 恩在最终决定亲自为爸爸动刀，此消息传遍医疗船，大家都表示愿意帮忙。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190829190000 +0800" stop="20190829200000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">黄金光辉的人生 My Golden Life  - EP 19</title>
    <desc lang="en">Zhi-an does not dare to tell Mingxi the truth about her identity when she witnesses how Mingxi treats those who betray her.  (PG)(双声道-中/韩)知安目睹明熙如何残忍地对待出卖她的画廊理事，于是不敢说出美静欺骗海成集团的事。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190829200000 +0800" stop="20190829210000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">黄金光辉的人生 My Golden Life  - EP 20</title>
    <desc lang="en">Photographs of Daojing touring a museum with Zhi-an are uploaded onto the company's intranet. The company staff speculate that Zhi-an was made a permanent staff because she is Daojing's girlfriend. Yanghao orders for Zhi-an's identity to be made public to squash the rumours.  (PG)(双声道-中/韩)知安和道京两人一起到博物馆游览的照片被人上载到公司的网站上，立刻引发热烈的讨论。大家谣传知安是道京的女友才得以顺利当上海成服饰的正职员工。为了杜绝谣言，阳浩下令马上公开知安的身份。.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190829210000 +0800" stop="20190829220000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">线人 3 Fixer 3 - EP 3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Under the influence of the Belt and Road Initiative in 2016, Sihanoukville has become a hot destination in Cambodia for the Chinese investors.  How do the Cambodian people strike balance on the original farming activities, livelihood, education and environmental issues with development and profits?  在2016年一带一路政策的影响下，大量的中资进入柬埔寨，而在濒临海港的西哈努克市，就成了中资们炙手可热的投资胜地。在发展与利润面前，柬埔寨人原本的农耕活动、民生、教育和环境问题，如何取得平衡？.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190829220000 +0800" stop="20190829230000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">你那边怎样.我这边OK  - 台湾篇 All Is Well - Taiwan - EP 4</title>
    <desc lang="en">Eric suspects that Justin had planned to involve him in the ATM hacking case, so he tries to contact him but Justin has cut off contact. Wei Yun finds a Teng Sheng Bank name card in Eric's clothes, and various signs lead her to suspect that Eric is involved in the ATM hacking case. She secretly goes on a yacht that Eric has rented to find clues for her report, but she accidentally encounters Ma Dong Bao, a killer hired by Li Hao...... Eric怀疑Justin设计害他卷入ATM盗领案，尝试联络他，但Justin已完全失联。维芸从Eric的衣服中发现腾升银行的名片，根据种种迹象让她拼凑出Eric涉嫌盗领案。她偷偷溜上Eric租的游艇，想找线索报道，不料遇见李昊派来的杀手马东宝…….</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20190829230000 +0800" stop="20190829233000 +0800" channel="Channel U">
    <title lang="en">晚间新闻 News Tonight</title>
    <desc lang="en">A comprehensive half-hour news programme, NEWS TONIGHT provides viewers with important local, international and financial developments for the day. U频道《晚间新闻》，在半小时里除深入报道本地与国际要闻，还有详尽的财经新闻和体坛动态。世界局势与经济动脉，让大家轻松掌握。.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>